

# SWETHA DAMARLA

**UI** Developer

#### About Me

Having 2.7 years of experience working as a UI Developer. My responsibilities included understanding client briefs, estimating and resourcing. Developed web applications that utilizes industry best practices, company standards and leverages latest web technologies Ensured to adapt and deliver quality deliverables requests. Involved in tracking and fixing defects if any and help business team with analyzing and categorizing defects.



7483426679



swetha.ece417@gmail.com

#### LANGUAGE

- English
- Telugu

#### **SKILLS SUMMARY**

- HTML, CSS,BOOTSTRAP
- Basic Knowledge on JavaScript, WordPress

#### **EXPERTISE**

- Time management
- Clear communication
- Self-motivated

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Sincro Digital Marketing(INDIA) pvt ltd HTML Developer July 2022 - February 2023

- Built layouts according to customer parameters using HTML5 and CSS3.
- Validated code for proper structuring, security and compatibility with different browsers, devices or operating systems
- Develop web applications that utilizes industry best practices, company standards and leverages latest web technologies.

### AARWII TECH SOLUTIONS PVT LTD HTML Developer April 2020 - April 2022

- Deliver best-in-class HTML5/CSS front-end code across abroad array of interactive web projects.
- Built layouts according to customer parameters using HTML5 and CSS3.
- Reviewed project specifications and devised solutions for use across multiple websites.

#### **EDUCATION**

## PSCMR College of Engineering and Technology

Bachelor of Science - Electronics And Communications Engineering 2011-2015